birthdays-calendar.com 2014-08-12

# Privacy Policy - member & reminder information never compromised

|  **Privacy & Security Policy **  
---  
Rest assured that your account and personal information are safe and secure at Birthday Calendar.  Your trust and privacy is important to us.  Your personal information is treated with great care and respect.

NO SPAM or Unsolicited E-mails - We only send user requested email and cell phone reminders and periodic emails regarding your account and services. 

Privacy - We will absolutely not share nor sell your personally identifiable information with/to any third party. 

Security - We take all precautions to protect your information via encryption software and other security practices. 

* * *

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Birthday Calendar.

Birthday Calendar is commited to your privacy and is determined to respect your trust and confidence.  At Birthday Calendar we agree to notify you of:  
  
|  What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site   
---|---  
|  The organization collecting the information   
|  How the information is used   
|  With whom the information may be shared   
|  What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
|  The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Birthday Calendar control   
|  How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information   
  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact [privacy@birthdays-calendar.com](mailto:privacy@birthdays-calendar.com).  **Information Collection and Use**   
Birthday Calendar is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Birthday Calendar collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  **Registration**   
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide billing information (such as credit card number), and other information (such as interests and hobbies), but encouraged so we can provide a more efficient and personalized experience on our site.  **Order**   
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user may provide recipient contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.  **Cookies/Clear GIFs**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they will not be able to use our site. 

Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users.

In conjunction with our third-party service partners, we make limited use of cookies and clear GIFs to gather information when you visit our sites, make a purchase and when you click through to our site from a targeted email, newsletter or partner site. We may also use cookies and clear GIFs to gather and compile such information about you when you return to our site so that we may better customize our services to you. 

**Log Files**   
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  **Sharing/Selling**   
Your birthday may be shared with friends that send you their birthday. 

We may share or sell 

_aggregated_ (not personal) demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is NOT linked to any personal information (such as last names, email addresses, street addresses, credit card numbers, etc) that can identify any individual person. 

We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. For example: 1.) a Paper Greeting Card supplier will need a Return & Ship To: address to fulfill an order, 2.) an Ecard provider will need to be supplied with the Recipient & Sender's email address.) 

**Legal Disclaimer**   
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.  **Links**   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at Birthday Calendar are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  **Email and Phone Reminders**   
If a user wishes to subscribe to our email reminders or phone reminders, we ask for contact information such as name, email address, and cell phone email address.  **Interest, Hobbies, and other Attributes**   
Information such as interest, hobbies, and other attributes both from and member and their recipients play a vital role for the recommendation engine to offer tailored suggestions of goods and services. This information is completely optional and is required only if the member desires specifically tailored suggestions of greeting cards, gifts, and other goods and services.  **Share your Reminders**   
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask for the friend's name and email address. Birthday Calendar will automatically send the friend email(s) inviting them to visit and join the site. Birthday Calendar will not use this information to send promotional emails.  **Security**   
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. Click here to verify our 

[Secured Site Certification](https://seal.godaddy.com/verifySeal?sealID=646827724018e80a6127102cc81da3117cee020482598007245261). 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@birthdays-calendar.com](mailto:security@birthdays-calendar.com). 

**Shopping**   
You must become a member to purchase anything from Birthday Calendar.  **Special Offers**   
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications by updating [My Privacy Preferences](http://www.birthday-calendar.com/memberscorner/myprivacypreferences.asp) options.  **Site and Service Updates**   
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.  **Correction/Updating Personal Information**   
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support.  **Opt-in/Opt-out**   
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-in' and 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes directly and indirectly related to our site like periodic updates on special promotions, communications directly with user "recipients" and the sharing or sale of non-personally identifiable information to third parties. Users can easily update their privacy preference options at any time in [My Privacy Preferences](http://www.birthday-calendar.com/memberscorner/myprivacypreferences.asp). 

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line to [unsubscribe@birthdays-calendar.com](mailto:unsubscribe@birthdays-calendar.com) or by simply updating their My Privacy Preferences options. 

**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  **Questions & More Information**   
If you have any questions or need more information regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Birthday Calendar  
154 East Prospect Avenue, Suite B  
Danville, CA 94526
